<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gist</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation</string>
    <string name="cse_about">Department of Computer Science &amp; Engineering was established in the year 2008 with an intake of 60 students and subsequently in the year 2011 the intake was increased to 120 students. The Department will be the centre of Excellence with competent facility, State-of-Art laboratory equipment, and adequate infrastructure with the faculty strengths to mould the students into leaders in their progression, the college has equipped with excellent computing facilities with cutting edge technology.
    We are Aware of the ever evolving nature of the field; the Department of Computer Science &amp; Engineering envisages a comprehensive structured programme through innovative and interactive strategies for keeping the students abreast with the changing trends and technologies and to constantly update and upgrade their skills to be industry-ready, by fostering necessary employable competencies.</string>
    <string name="ece_about">Department of Electronics and Communication Engineering (ECE) was established in the year 2008 and offers an under graduate program in Electronics and Communication Engineering, with an initial intake of 60, and progressively increased to 180 by the year 2012. To accomplish the mission and vision of the Department, it has adequate infrastructural support with well equipped laboratories and Licensed softwares comprises Xilinx, Code Composer Studio, MATLAB, LABTEK, MASM etc., .

The Department aims at imparting the students with the latest technologies through NPTEL online resources, Webinars by Texas Instruments, Spoken tutorials, SWAYAM and FOSSEE by IIT Bombay, Lab VIEW in association with National Instruments (NI),  Workshops and internships in association with Andhra Pradesh State Skill Development Corporation (APSSDC) etc.,
Endowed with a cluster of well qualified, proficient and highly stimulating faculty including 8 Doctorates and 23 M.Tech graduates in the specialized areas of VLSI Desin, Digital Electronics and Computer systems, and Embedded systems adopting some of the best academic practices like Smart Classrooms and ICT methods.</string>
    <string name="eee_about">The Electrical and Electronics Engineering Department, established in the year 2008, has been well structured. The department is running with well qualified, dedicated and experienced faculty. All faculty are with minimum M.Tech qualification to fulfill the aspirations of student community.

It is offering B.Tech. (EEE)  programme with an annual intake of 60 and providing outstanding facilities for all the students to learn innovative technologies.

The department has exclusive departmental library with large number of titles and volumes. The library has Intranet/Internet facilities to access AUTOLIB , OPAC , NPTEL and online journals.The department has a student forum EEA (Electrical Engineers Association) and IE-I (Institution of Engineers – India), a professional students chapter for conducting career developing inter-personal and intra-personal skills of students. It organizes Seminars, Quiz Programmes, Industrial Visits, Paper Contests, Group Discussions, Guest Lectures, Career Guidance, and Games etc under its auspices.

As a part of the curriculum, Industrial visits are arranged for students to upgrade their skill and knowledge. Our EEE students also actively participated in paper presentation contest organized at various Engineering Colleges and Universities. Some of them have been awarded in these Paper presentation contests.</string>
    <string name="civil_about">Department of Civil Engineering was established in the year 2010 with an intake of 60 students and subsequently in the year 2012 the intake was increased to 120 students. The department unveiled another programme 3 year Diploma in Civil Engineering with an intake of 60 students in the year 2014. The course offers a deep insight into the discipline and enables promising engineers to acquire skills required to succeed both individually as well as in Industry. The department is committed to well being and all round development of its students. The department is very well equipped with 9 laboratories and computational facilities.</string>
    <string name="mech_about">Department of Mechanical Engineering is established in the year 2010 offers programmes to enable promising engineers to acquire skills required to succeed both individually as well as in Industry. The department has started 4 year B.Tech programme in Mechanical Engineering under JNTUA affiliation, with an intake of 60 students in the year 2010 and subsequently in the year 2014, the department unveiled another programme 3 year Diploma in Mechanical Engineering under SBTET, AP affiliation with an intake of 60 students.</string>

    <string name="sandh_about">Department of Science and Humanities provides the solid foundation for the students in reorienting them towards technical education, equipping them with knowledge in basic engineering streams and exposing them to a broad spectrum of subjects and disciplines like Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry, Environmental Sciences and Management studies in addition to extensive training in Language and Communication Skills. The creative, critical, analytical and communicative faculties of the students are sharpened and fine-tuned.The department is sufficiently supported and strengthened with well experienced members of faculty handling the subtleties making the students sensitive to the finer nuances of the concepts taught. All Laboratories are fully equipped to conduct the experiments as per the syllabus prescribed by the University. The language laboratories are provided with facilities for playing audio/video files, PA system and DLP projector along with interactive software for in-depth training and practice of the students. Unique additional value inputs are imparted in the areas of personality development, communication and soft skills.\n

 </string>
    <string name="placements">1.    Understanding the needs of the Industry and demands of the community and making the students themselves to relate with the work.
\n\n2.	Identifying the needs and problems of the community / society and make the students involve solving the problems.\n
\n3.	Counsel the students on career development.\n
\n4.	Organize campus drives to create various opportunities and improve campus placements.\n
\n5.	Provide ample training programmes to improve Personality Development, Aptitude, Verbal, Logical, Quantitative and Communication and Soft skills.\n
\n6.	Conduct online assessments and track the student results to provide specific training.\n
\n7.	Update the strategies from time to time to ensure good placements.\n
\n8.	Maintaining cordial relationship with the corporate and industry.\n
\n9.	Train the students on their future career opportunities/prospects.\n
\n10.	Organize training programmes, guest lectures, and mock tests for recruitment.\n
\n11.	Displaying  various job advertisements.\n
\n12.	Encourage the students and impart training in the trending technologies.\n
\n13.	Motivate the students to explore opportunities either through online sources or career columns in news papers.\n
</string>
    <string name="admission">The admission pattern to B. Tech:\n\n

        The minimum qualification for admission to first year of the B. Tech course is a pass in the Intermediate (10 + 2) conducted by the board of Intermediate education, Govt. of AP State or any other examination recognized as equivalent thereto with Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry as optional subjects. Admissions to the Institute are made along with the other Engineering colleges in the state through a common entrance test (EAMCET) conducted by the Govt. of AP State.

        \n\n\n70 % of the seats are allotted based on the merit in the AP EAMCET (A-Category).
        \n\n30% of the seats are earmarked for NRI/Management candidates (B-Category).\n

        \n\nThe admission pattern to B. Tech. Lateral Entry (LES):

        \nDiploma holders are admitted in second year of B. Tech to the extent of 10% of intake based on the merit in the AP ECET, under lateral entry scheme.
        \n\nDiploma :\n

        \nThe minimum qualification for admission to first year of the Diploma course is a pass in the 10th conducted by the Board of Secondary Education, Govt. of Andhra Pradesh or any other examination recognized as equivalent. Admissions to the College are made along with the other Engineering Colleges in the state through a common entrance test AP POLYCET conducted by the Govt. of Andhra Pradesh.
       \n\nScholarships:

        \n\nGIST believes in extending full support to deserving students who work really hard to accomplish their goals. The college offers merit-cum-mean scholarships for those deserving Students who cannot afford to pay the tuition/hostel/transport fees.
    </string>
    <string name="origin"><b>Origins of New Horizons :-</b> \n\n
Ushodaya Educational Society, with decades of experience and expertise in running educational Institutes established Geethanjali Institute of Science and Technology in order to provide quality Engineering and Technical Education to the rural and underprivileged lot on par with the creamy layer of society. The College is well connected by road with NH5 at 3 KM and Mumbai State High way at about 500 Meters away. The nearest Railhead is just 5 KM away. A network of roads and a variety of transport options at regular frequency, make it accessible from different places.

\n\nLocated in a picturesque lush landscape amidst aesthetic ambience near Nellore, it provides right teaching-learning environment. The Institution is approved by AICTE, New Delhi, affiliated to Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Anantapur.

\n\nGIST envisages comprehensive development of the students and offers qualitative, enduring, enriching, educational experience making it a dynamic hub of academic excellence, vibrant with inventive and innovative practices and teaching-learning strategies.

        \n\n\n<b>Vision :-</b>\n\n
To emerge as a leading Engineering institution imparting quality education
        \n\n\n<b>Mission :-</b> \n\n
Effective teaching-learning strategies for quality education
\nCongenial academic ambience for progressive learning
\nSkill development through Industry-Institute initiatives
\nNurturing environmentally conscious and socially responsible technocrats</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>